[
    {
        "question_no.": 1,
        "Question": "Which British chef is known for his fiery temper and is a star of shows like 'Hell's Kitchen' and 'Kitchen Nightmares'?",
        "Option1": "Jamie Oliver",
        "Option2": "Gordon Ramsay",
        "Option3": "Heston Blumenthal",
        "Option4": "Tom Kerridge",
        "Answer": "Gordon Ramsay"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 2,
        "Question": "The classic cookbook 'Mastering the Art of French Cooking' was co-authored by which American chef who brought French cuisine to the masses?",
        "Option1": "Ina Garten",
        "Option2": "Rachael Ray",
        "Option3": "Julia Child",
        "Option4": "Giada De Laurentiis",
        "Answer": "Julia Child"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 3,
        "Question": "Who is the host of 'The Naked Chef' and is famous for his simple, rustic, and fresh approach to cooking?",
        "Option1": "Gordon Ramsay",
        "Option2": "Jamie Oliver",
        "Option3": "Emeril Lagasse",
        "Option4": "Marco Pierre White",
        "Answer": "Jamie Oliver"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 4,
        "Question": "Which celebrity chef is famous for his signature catchphrases like 'Bam!' and 'Kick it up a notch!'?",
        "Option1": "Bobby Flay",
        "Option2": "Guy Fieri",
        "Option3": "Emeril Lagasse",
        "Option4": "Wolfgang Puck",
        "Answer": "Emeril Lagasse"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 5,
        "Question": "Known for his food-travel shows like 'No Reservations' and 'Parts Unknown,' which chef and author tragically passed away in 2018?",
        "Option1": "Anthony Bourdain",
        "Option2": "José Andrés",
        "Option3": "David Chang",
        "Option4": "Andrew Zimmern",
        "Answer": "Anthony Bourdain"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 6,
        "Question": "Which Austrian-American chef is best known for his fine dining restaurants and for popularizing 'California cuisine'?",
        "Option1": "Wolfgang Puck",
        "Option2": "Thomas Keller",
        "Option3": "Alain Ducasse",
        "Option4": "Daniel Boulud",
        "Answer": "Wolfgang Puck"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 7,
        "Question": "Who is the author of 'Barefoot Contessa,' and is known for her approachable recipes and television show on the Food Network?",
        "Option1": "Nigella Lawson",
        "Option2": "Ina Garten",
        "Option3": "Martha Stewart",
        "Option4": "Giada De Laurentiis",
        "Answer": "Ina Garten"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 8,
        "Question": "This American chef is a star of 'Beat Bobby Flay' and 'Iron Chef America,' and is known for his expertise in Southwestern and Tex-Mex cuisine.",
        "Option1": "Bobby Flay",
        "Option2": "Alton Brown",
        "Option3": "Michael Symon",
        "Option4": "Alex Guarnaschelli",
        "Answer": "Bobby Flay"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 9,
        "Question": "Which Food Network personality is known for his spiky hair, vintage car, and for traveling the country on 'Diners, Drive-Ins and Dives'?",
        "Option1": "Guy Fieri",
        "Option2": "Andrew Zimmern",
        "Option3": "Michael Symon",
        "Option4": "Tyler Florence",
        "Answer": "Guy Fieri"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 10,
        "Question": "Which late French chef, known as the 'Chef of the Century,' was the most decorated with Michelin stars in the world?",
        "Option1": "Paul Bocuse",
        "Option2": "Auguste Escoffier",
        "Option3": "Alain Ducasse",
        "Option4": "Joël Robuchon",
        "Answer": "Joël Robuchon"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 11,
        "Question": "Which chef's restaurant, The Fat Duck, is known for its multi-sensory and 'molecular gastronomy' approach?",
        "Option1": "Ferran Adrià",
        "Option2": "Massimo Bottura",
        "Option3": "Heston Blumenthal",
        "Option4": "Grant Achatz",
        "Answer": "Heston Blumenthal"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 12,
        "Question": "Which Spanish chef is credited with pioneering 'molecular gastronomy' and turning his restaurant, elBulli, into a legendary culinary destination?",
        "Option1": "José Andrés",
        "Option2": "Ferran Adrià",
        "Option3": "Dabiz Muñoz",
        "Option4": "Andoni Luis Aduriz",
        "Answer": "Ferran Adrià"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 13,
        "Question": "Often called the 'father of modern French cuisine,' this chef's restaurant, L'Auberge du Pont de Collonges, held three Michelin stars for over 50 years.",
        "Option1": "Paul Bocuse",
        "Option2": "Auguste Escoffier",
        "Option3": "Joël Robuchon",
        "Option4": "Alain Ducasse",
        "Answer": "Paul Bocuse"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 14,
        "Question": "Which American chef and restaurateur is known for her pivotal role in the 'farm-to-table' movement with her restaurant, Chez Panisse, in Berkeley, California?",
        "Option1": "Julia Child",
        "Option2": "Nancy Silverton",
        "Option3": "Alice Waters",
        "Option4": "Lidia Bastianich",
        "Answer": "Alice Waters"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 15,
        "Question": "Who is known as the 'Emperor of the World's Kitchens' and standardized French cuisine with his extensive system of 'Le Guide Culinaire'?",
        "Option1": "Paul Bocuse",
        "Option2": "Auguste Escoffier",
        "Option3": "Joël Robuchon",
        "Option4": "Georges Auguste Escoffier",
        "Answer": "Auguste Escoffier"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 16,
        "Question": "Which Italian chef is the proprietor of Osteria Francescana, a three-Michelin-star restaurant in Modena, Italy, known for its creative and whimsical dishes?",
        "Option1": "Carlo Cracco",
        "Option2": "Massimo Bottura",
        "Option3": "Enrico Bartolini",
        "Option4": "Niko Romito",
        "Answer": "Massimo Bottura"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 17,
        "Question": "This chef from Denmark gained international fame for his restaurant Noma, known for its focus on foraging and New Nordic cuisine.",
        "Option1": "Claus Meyer",
        "Option2": "René Redzepi",
        "Option3": "Rasmus Kofoed",
        "Option4": "Magnus Nilsson",
        "Answer": "René Redzepi"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 18,
        "Question": "Which Indian chef and television personality is credited with popularizing Indian cuisine globally through his shows and cookbooks?",
        "Option1": "Vikas Khanna",
        "Option2": "Sanjeev Kapoor",
        "Option3": "Ranveer Brar",
        "Option4": "Madhur Jaffrey",
        "Answer": "Sanjeev Kapoor"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 19,
        "Question": "Known for his avant-garde, 'molecular gastronomy' techniques, which American chef runs the three-Michelin-star restaurant Alinea in Chicago?",
        "Option1": "Grant Achatz",
        "Option2": "Daniel Humm",
        "Option3": "David Chang",
        "Option4": "Thomas Keller",
        "Answer": "Grant Achatz"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 20,
        "Question": "Which chef is the proprietor of El Celler de Can Roca, a restaurant in Girona, Spain, known for its use of technology in cooking and its three brothers who run it?",
        "Option1": "Juan Mari Arzak",
        "Option2": "Ferran Adrià",
        "Option3": "Joan Roca",
        "Option4": "Andoni Luis Aduriz",
        "Answer": "Joan Roca"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 21,
        "Question": "The chef behind the Momofuku restaurant group, this American chef is a major figure in the modern American food scene.",
        "Option1": "David Chang",
        "Option2": "Danny Meyer",
        "Option3": "Thomas Keller",
        "Option4": "Mario Batali",
        "Answer": "David Chang"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 22,
        "Question": "Which chef is the head of the restaurant Eleven Madison Park in New York City, known for its high-end, plant-based tasting menu?",
        "Option1": "Grant Achatz",
        "Option2": "Eric Ripert",
        "Option3": "Daniel Humm",
        "Option4": "Wylie Dufresne",
        "Answer": "Daniel Humm"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 23,
        "Question": "This chef, born in Ethiopia and raised in Sweden, is known for his creative fusion of diverse cuisines, showcased in his restaurant Red Rooster in Harlem.",
        "Option1": "Marcus Samuelsson",
        "Option2": "Eric Ripert",
        "Option3": "José Andrés",
        "Option4": "Daniel Boulud",
        "Answer": "Marcus Samuelsson"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 24,
        "Question": "Known for his humanitarian efforts and the World Central Kitchen, which Spanish-American chef and restaurateur provides food relief after natural disasters?",
        "Option1": "Ferran Adrià",
        "Option2": "José Andrés",
        "Option3": "Alain Ducasse",
        "Option4": "Martín Berasategui",
        "Answer": "José Andrés"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 25,
        "Question": "Which chef is the proprietor of the three-Michelin-star restaurant The French Laundry in Yountville, California?",
        "Option1": "Daniel Humm",
        "Option2": "Thomas Keller",
        "Option3": "Eric Ripert",
        "Option4": "Grant Achatz",
        "Answer": "Thomas Keller"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 26,
        "Question": "Which British chef is known for his restaurant 'Restaurant Gordon Ramsay' which has held three Michelin stars since 2001?",
        "Option1": "Jamie Oliver",
        "Option2": "Heston Blumenthal",
        "Option3": "Marco Pierre White",
        "Option4": "Gordon Ramsay",
        "Answer": "Gordon Ramsay"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 27,
        "Question": "Known as the 'Dean of American Cookery,' which chef and food writer was a pioneer in using local, seasonal ingredients?",
        "Option1": "Julia Child",
        "Option2": "James Beard",
        "Option3": "Craig Claiborne",
        "Option4": "M.F.K. Fisher",
        "Answer": "James Beard"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 28,
        "Question": "Which celebrity chef is known for her catchphrase 'EVOO' and her '30 Minute Meals' television show?",
        "Option1": "Ina Garten",
        "Option2": "Giada De Laurentiis",
        "Option3": "Rachael Ray",
        "Option4": "Paula Deen",
        "Answer": "Rachael Ray"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 29,
        "Question": "This American restaurateur and television personality is known for her successful restaurants and as a judge on 'Top Chef'.",
        "Option1": "Cat Cora",
        "Option2": "Carla Hall",
        "Option3": "Gail Simmons",
        "Option4": "Lidia Bastianich",
        "Answer": "Gail Simmons"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 30,
        "Question": "Who is the proprietor of Nobu, a chain of high-end Japanese restaurants known for their unique fusion cuisine?",
        "Option1": "Masaharu Morimoto",
        "Option2": "Nobu Matsuhisa",
        "Option3": "Tetsuya Wakuda",
        "Option4": "Jiro Ono",
        "Answer": "Nobu Matsuhisa"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 31,
        "Question": "Which American television personality is known for 'Good Eats,' a show that explores the science and history behind food?",
        "Option1": "Michael Symon",
        "Option2": "Tyler Florence",
        "Option3": "Alton Brown",
        "Option4": "Alex Guarnaschelli",
        "Answer": "Alton Brown"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 32,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for his three-Michelin-star restaurant Le Bernardin in New York City, specializing in refined French seafood?",
        "Option1": "Thomas Keller",
        "Option2": "Eric Ripert",
        "Option3": "Daniel Boulud",
        "Option4": "Alain Ducasse",
        "Answer": "Eric Ripert"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 33,
        "Question": "This French-born, New York-based chef is known for his restaurant Daniel, and for being a master of contemporary French cuisine.",
        "Option1": "Jean-Georges Vongerichten",
        "Option2": "Alain Ducasse",
        "Option3": "Daniel Boulud",
        "Option4": "Joël Robuchon",
        "Answer": "Daniel Boulud"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 34,
        "Question": "Which British chef became the youngest chef ever to be awarded three Michelin stars?",
        "Option1": "Jamie Oliver",
        "Option2": "Gordon Ramsay",
        "Option3": "Marco Pierre White",
        "Option4": "Heston Blumenthal",
        "Answer": "Marco Pierre White"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 35,
        "Question": "Known for his minimalist cooking style and the documentary 'Jiro Dreams of Sushi,' which Japanese sushi master is considered a national treasure?",
        "Option1": "Masaharu Morimoto",
        "Option2": "Nobu Matsuhisa",
        "Option3": "Yoshihiro Murata",
        "Option4": "Jiro Ono",
        "Answer": "Jiro Ono"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 36,
        "Question": "Who is the host of 'Barefoot Contessa' on Food Network and the author of several popular cookbooks?",
        "Option1": "Nigella Lawson",
        "Option2": "Giada De Laurentiis",
        "Option3": "Ina Garten",
        "Option4": "Paula Deen",
        "Answer": "Ina Garten"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 37,
        "Question": "Which chef is the proprietor of the three-Michelin-star restaurant El Celler de Can Roca in Girona, Spain?",
        "Option1": "Ferran Adrià",
        "Option2": "Joan Roca",
        "Option3": "Andoni Luis Aduriz",
        "Option4": "Dabiz Muñoz",
        "Answer": "Joan Roca"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 38,
        "Question": "The chef and author who pioneered 'New American' cuisine, with his restaurant, Spago, in Beverly Hills, is whom?",
        "Option1": "Thomas Keller",
        "Option2": "Wolfgang Puck",
        "Option3": "Daniel Boulud",
        "Option4": "Bobby Flay",
        "Answer": "Wolfgang Puck"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 39,
        "Question": "Which American chef is known for his work with the Momofuku restaurant group and for creating the television series 'Ugly Delicious'?",
        "Option1": "Grant Achatz",
        "Option2": "David Chang",
        "Option3": "Daniel Humm",
        "Option4": "José Andrés",
        "Answer": "David Chang"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 40,
        "Question": "Who is the co-owner of the restaurant 'L'Auberge du Pont de Collonges' which held three Michelin stars for over 50 years?",
        "Option1": "Joël Robuchon",
        "Option2": "Paul Bocuse",
        "Option3": "Alain Ducasse",
        "Option4": "Auguste Escoffier",
        "Answer": "Paul Bocuse"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 41,
        "Question": "This chef is the owner of the three-Michelin-star restaurant 'Eleven Madison Park' and is a proponent of plant-based cuisine.",
        "Option1": "Daniel Humm",
        "Option2": "Thomas Keller",
        "Option3": "Eric Ripert",
        "Option4": "Grant Achatz",
        "Answer": "Daniel Humm"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 42,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for his television shows like 'Diners, Drive-Ins and Dives' and 'Guy's Grocery Games'?",
        "Option1": "Bobby Flay",
        "Option2": "Alton Brown",
        "Option3": "Michael Symon",
        "Option4": "Guy Fieri",
        "Answer": "Guy Fieri"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 43,
        "Question": "Who is the founder of World Central Kitchen, a non-profit organization that provides meals in response to humanitarian crises?",
        "Option1": "José Andrés",
        "Option2": "Massimo Bottura",
        "Option3": "René Redzepi",
        "Option4": "Marcus Samuelsson",
        "Answer": "José Andrés"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 44,
        "Question": "This chef is famous for his multi-sensory and 'molecular gastronomy' techniques, with a signature dish called 'Snail Porridge'.",
        "Option1": "Ferran Adrià",
        "Option2": "Heston Blumenthal",
        "Option3": "Massimo Bottura",
        "Option4": "Grant Achatz",
        "Answer": "Heston Blumenthal"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 45,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for bringing French haute cuisine to the masses through her television show 'The French Chef'?",
        "Option1": "Ina Garten",
        "Option2": "Julia Child",
        "Option3": "Lidia Bastianich",
        "Option4": "Rachael Ray",
        "Answer": "Julia Child"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 46,
        "Question": "Who is the proprietor of the restaurant The French Laundry, a renowned fine-dining establishment in California's Napa Valley?",
        "Option1": "Daniel Humm",
        "Option2": "Thomas Keller",
        "Option3": "Eric Ripert",
        "Option4": "Grant Achatz",
        "Answer": "Thomas Keller"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 47,
        "Question": "This chef is a native of Sicily and is known for her classic Italian dishes and her show 'Everyday Italian'.",
        "Option1": "Rachael Ray",
        "Option2": "Lidia Bastianich",
        "Option3": "Giada De Laurentiis",
        "Option4": "Ina Garten",
        "Answer": "Giada De Laurentiis"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 48,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for her cookbooks and television show 'Nigella Bites'?",
        "Option1": "Delia Smith",
        "Option2": "Nigella Lawson",
        "Option3": "Mary Berry",
        "Option4": "Jamie Oliver",
        "Answer": "Nigella Lawson"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 49,
        "Question": "Who is the host of 'Cutthroat Kitchen' and is known for his dry wit and scientific approach to cooking?",
        "Option1": "Bobby Flay",
        "Option2": "Michael Symon",
        "Option3": "Alton Brown",
        "Option4": "Tyler Florence",
        "Answer": "Alton Brown"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 50,
        "Question": "Which chef and television personality is known for 'The Chew' and for her southern cooking style?",
        "Option1": "Carla Hall",
        "Option2": "Cat Cora",
        "Option3": "Alex Guarnaschelli",
        "Option4": "Giada De Laurentiis",
        "Answer": "Carla Hall"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 51,
        "Question": "Which chef is the proprietor of Alinea, a three-Michelin-star restaurant in Chicago known for its highly experimental cuisine?",
        "Option1": "Grant Achatz",
        "Option2": "Thomas Keller",
        "Option3": "José Andrés",
        "Option4": "Daniel Humm",
        "Answer": "Grant Achatz"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 52,
        "Question": "Who is the author of 'Ad Hoc at Home' and the chef behind the famous 'The French Laundry'?",
        "Option1": "Eric Ripert",
        "Option2": "Thomas Keller",
        "Option3": "Daniel Boulud",
        "Option4": "Wolfgang Puck",
        "Answer": "Thomas Keller"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 53,
        "Question": "Which chef is the proprietor of the three-Michelin-star restaurant Osteria Francescana in Modena, Italy?",
        "Option1": "Massimo Bottura",
        "Option2": "Carlo Cracco",
        "Option3": "Enrico Bartolini",
        "Option4": "Davide Oldani",
        "Answer": "Massimo Bottura"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 54,
        "Question": "Known for his television show 'Bizarre Foods,' which chef is famous for traveling the world and trying unusual and exotic dishes?",
        "Option1": "Anthony Bourdain",
        "Option2": "Guy Fieri",
        "Option3": "Andrew Zimmern",
        "Option4": "Adam Richman",
        "Answer": "Andrew Zimmern"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 55,
        "Question": "Who is the chef behind the restaurant Noma in Copenhagen, which has repeatedly been named the 'World's Best Restaurant'?",
        "Option1": "René Redzepi",
        "Option2": "Claus Meyer",
        "Option3": "Rasmus Kofoed",
        "Option4": "Magnus Nilsson",
        "Answer": "René Redzepi"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 56,
        "Question": "Which chef is credited with inventing the sous-vide cooking method, and is the founder of the restaurant El Celler de Can Roca?",
        "Option1": "Joan Roca",
        "Option2": "Ferran Adrià",
        "Option3": "José Andrés",
        "Option4": "Carme Ruscalleda",
        "Answer": "Joan Roca"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 57,
        "Question": "Known for his humanitarian work and for bringing Spanish cuisine to the U.S., which chef is the founder of the World Central Kitchen?",
        "Option1": "José Andrés",
        "Option2": "Massimo Bottura",
        "Option3": "René Redzepi",
        "Option4": "Marcus Samuelsson",
        "Answer": "José Andrés"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 58,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for his modern and innovative take on Indian cuisine, with his restaurant Gaggan in Bangkok?",
        "Option1": "Sanjeev Kapoor",
        "Option2": "Vikas Khanna",
        "Option3": "Gaggan Anand",
        "Option4": "Ranveer Brar",
        "Answer": "Gaggan Anand"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 59,
        "Question": "Who is the proprietor of the three-Michelin-star restaurant Le Bernardin in New York City?",
        "Option1": "Thomas Keller",
        "Option2": "Eric Ripert",
        "Option3": "Daniel Boulud",
        "Option4": "Alain Ducasse",
        "Answer": "Eric Ripert"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 60,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for his simple and rustic Italian-American cuisine and his role as a co-host of 'The Chew'?",
        "Option1": "Giada De Laurentiis",
        "Option2": "Mario Batali",
        "Option3": "Michael Symon",
        "Option4": "Rocco DiSpirito",
        "Answer": "Michael Symon"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 61,
        "Question": "Known for her Southern-style cooking and her show 'Paula's Best Dishes,' which celebrity chef faced controversy in 2013?",
        "Option1": "Pioneer Woman",
        "Option2": "Paula Deen",
        "Option3": "Trisha Yearwood",
        "Option4": "Sandra Lee",
        "Answer": "Paula Deen"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 62,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for his classic French restaurant 'Daniel' in New York City?",
        "Option1": "Jean-Georges Vongerichten",
        "Option2": "Alain Ducasse",
        "Option3": "Daniel Boulud",
        "Option4": "Thomas Keller",
        "Answer": "Daniel Boulud"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 63,
        "Question": "This chef is the host of 'The F Word' and 'MasterChef,' and is known for his high standards and fiery temper.",
        "Option1": "Jamie Oliver",
        "Option2": "Gordon Ramsay",
        "Option3": "Heston Blumenthal",
        "Option4": "Marco Pierre White",
        "Answer": "Gordon Ramsay"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 64,
        "Question": "The chef behind the 'farm-to-table' movement, which chef founded the restaurant 'Chez Panisse'?",
        "Option1": "Julia Child",
        "Option2": "Alice Waters",
        "Option3": "Ina Garten",
        "Option4": "Nancy Silverton",
        "Answer": "Alice Waters"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 65,
        "Question": "Which chef is famous for his television show '30 Minute Meals' and for popularizing easy, everyday cooking?",
        "Option1": "Ina Garten",
        "Option2": "Giada De Laurentiis",
        "Option3": "Rachael Ray",
        "Option4": "Paula Deen",
        "Answer": "Rachael Ray"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 66,
        "Question": "Who is the owner of the restaurant 'Mugaritz' in Spain, known for its creative and experimental cuisine?",
        "Option1": "Ferran Adrià",
        "Option2": "Joan Roca",
        "Option3": "Andoni Luis Aduriz",
        "Option4": "Dabiz Muñoz",
        "Answer": "Andoni Luis Aduriz"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 67,
        "Question": "Which American chef is known for his television shows like 'Iron Chef America' and for his focus on Asian-fusion cuisine?",
        "Option1": "Bobby Flay",
        "Option2": "Alton Brown",
        "Option3": "Michael Symon",
        "Option4": "Masaharu Morimoto",
        "Answer": "Masaharu Morimoto"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 68,
        "Question": "Known for his restaurant 'Eleven Madison Park,' which chef turned his tasting menu into a fully plant-based experience?",
        "Option1": "Thomas Keller",
        "Option2": "Daniel Humm",
        "Option3": "Eric Ripert",
        "Option4": "Grant Achatz",
        "Answer": "Daniel Humm"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 69,
        "Question": "This chef, known as the 'original celebrity chef,' was the first to have her own cooking show on television.",
        "Option1": "Julia Child",
        "Option2": "Fanny Cradock",
        "Option3": "Mary Berry",
        "Option4": "Delia Smith",
        "Answer": "Julia Child"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 70,
        "Question": "Which chef's restaurant, 'El Bulli,' was a three-Michelin-star restaurant in Spain, known for its groundbreaking 'molecular gastronomy'?",
        "Option1": "Ferran Adrià",
        "Option2": "José Andrés",
        "Option3": "Massimo Bottura",
        "Option4": "Joan Roca",
        "Answer": "Ferran Adrià"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 71,
        "Question": "Who is the proprietor of 'The Fat Duck,' a restaurant known for its multi-sensory and 'molecular gastronomy' approach?",
        "Option1": "Ferran Adrià",
        "Option2": "Massimo Bottura",
        "Option3": "Heston Blumenthal",
        "Option4": "Grant Achatz",
        "Answer": "Heston Blumenthal"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 72,
        "Question": "This chef is the owner of 'L'Auberge du Pont de Collonges,' a restaurant that held three Michelin stars for over 50 years.",
        "Option1": "Joël Robuchon",
        "Option2": "Paul Bocuse",
        "Option3": "Alain Ducasse",
        "Option4": "Auguste Escoffier",
        "Answer": "Paul Bocuse"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 73,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for his television shows like 'Chef's Table' and 'Ugly Delicious'?",
        "Option1": "Daniel Humm",
        "Option2": "David Chang",
        "Option3": "Thomas Keller",
        "Option4": "José Andrés",
        "Answer": "David Chang"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 74,
        "Question": "The chef behind 'The French Laundry,' 'Per Se,' and 'Bouchon Bakery,' who is known for his meticulous attention to detail?",
        "Option1": "Eric Ripert",
        "Option2": "Thomas Keller",
        "Option3": "Daniel Boulud",
        "Option4": "Wolfgang Puck",
        "Answer": "Thomas Keller"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 75,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for his humanitarian work and for founding the World Central Kitchen?",
        "Option1": "José Andrés",
        "Option2": "Massimo Bottura",
        "Option3": "René Redzepi",
        "Option4": "Marcus Samuelsson",
        "Answer": "José Andrés"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 76,
        "Question": "This chef, born in Sweden, is known for his restaurant 'Red Rooster' in Harlem, New York, and for his fusion cooking style.",
        "Option1": "Eric Ripert",
        "Option2": "José Andrés",
        "Option3": "Marcus Samuelsson",
        "Option4": "Daniel Humm",
        "Answer": "Marcus Samuelsson"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 77,
        "Question": "Known for his popular television shows, which chef is the owner of multiple restaurants, including 'Maze' and 'Petrus'?",
        "Option1": "Jamie Oliver",
        "Option2": "Heston Blumenthal",
        "Option3": "Gordon Ramsay",
        "Option4": "Marco Pierre White",
        "Answer": "Gordon Ramsay"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 78,
        "Question": "Who is the proprietor of the three-Michelin-star restaurant 'Osteria Francescana' in Modena, Italy?",
        "Option1": "Massimo Bottura",
        "Option2": "Carlo Cracco",
        "Option3": "Enrico Bartolini",
        "Option4": "Davide Oldani",
        "Answer": "Massimo Bottura"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 79,
        "Question": "The chef behind the restaurant 'Noma,' which focuses on foraging and seasonal ingredients, is who?",
        "Option1": "Claus Meyer",
        "Option2": "René Redzepi",
        "Option3": "Rasmus Kofoed",
        "Option4": "Magnus Nilsson",
        "Answer": "René Redzepi"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 80,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for his television show 'Bizarre Foods' and for trying unusual and exotic dishes?",
        "Option1": "Anthony Bourdain",
        "Option2": "Guy Fieri",
        "Option3": "Andrew Zimmern",
        "Option4": "Adam Richman",
        "Answer": "Andrew Zimmern"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 81,
        "Question": "Which chef is known as the 'father of modern French cuisine'?",
        "Option1": "Paul Bocuse",
        "Option2": "Auguste Escoffier",
        "Option3": "Joël Robuchon",
        "Option4": "Alain Ducasse",
        "Answer": "Paul Bocuse"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 82,
        "Question": "Who is the proprietor of 'The French Laundry,' a three-Michelin-star restaurant in Yountville, California?",
        "Option1": "Daniel Humm",
        "Option2": "Thomas Keller",
        "Option3": "Eric Ripert",
        "Option4": "Grant Achatz",
        "Answer": "Thomas Keller"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 83,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for his humanitarian work with 'World Central Kitchen'?",
        "Option1": "José Andrés",
        "Option2": "Massimo Bottura",
        "Option3": "René Redzepi",
        "Option4": "Marcus Samuelsson",
        "Answer": "José Andrés"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 84,
        "Question": "The chef behind the 'Momofuku' restaurant group is who?",
        "Option1": "David Chang",
        "Option2": "Danny Meyer",
        "Option3": "Thomas Keller",
        "Option4": "Mario Batali",
        "Answer": "David Chang"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 85,
        "Question": "Which American chef is known for his 'Good Eats' television show, which focuses on the science and history of food?",
        "Option1": "Michael Symon",
        "Option2": "Alton Brown",
        "Option3": "Tyler Florence",
        "Option4": "Alex Guarnaschelli",
        "Answer": "Alton Brown"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 86,
        "Question": "Who is the proprietor of the three-Michelin-star restaurant 'Le Bernardin' in New York City, which specializes in seafood?",
        "Option1": "Thomas Keller",
        "Option2": "Eric Ripert",
        "Option3": "Daniel Boulud",
        "Option4": "Alain Ducasse",
        "Answer": "Eric Ripert"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 87,
        "Question": "This chef, born in Sweden, is known for his restaurant 'Red Rooster' in Harlem, New York.",
        "Option1": "Eric Ripert",
        "Option2": "José Andrés",
        "Option3": "Marcus Samuelsson",
        "Option4": "Daniel Humm",
        "Answer": "Marcus Samuelsson"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 88,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for her approachable recipes and her television show 'Barefoot Contessa'?",
        "Option1": "Nigella Lawson",
        "Option2": "Ina Garten",
        "Option3": "Giada De Laurentiis",
        "Option4": "Paula Deen",
        "Answer": "Ina Garten"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 89,
        "Question": "The chef and proprietor of 'Osteria Francescana' is who?",
        "Option1": "Carlo Cracco",
        "Option2": "Massimo Bottura",
        "Option3": "Enrico Bartolini",
        "Option4": "Davide Oldani",
        "Answer": "Massimo Bottura"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 90,
        "Question": "Which chef is famous for his television shows like 'Diners, Drive-Ins and Dives' and 'Guy's Grocery Games'?",
        "Option1": "Bobby Flay",
        "Option2": "Alton Brown",
        "Option3": "Michael Symon",
        "Option4": "Guy Fieri",
        "Answer": "Guy Fieri"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 91,
        "Question": "This chef is known for her book 'Mastering the Art of French Cooking' and her television show 'The French Chef'.",
        "Option1": "Ina Garten",
        "Option2": "Rachael Ray",
        "Option3": "Julia Child",
        "Option4": "Giada De Laurentiis",
        "Answer": "Julia Child"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 92,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for his restaurant 'El Bulli' and for pioneering 'molecular gastronomy'?",
        "Option1": "Ferran Adrià",
        "Option2": "José Andrés",
        "Option3": "Massimo Bottura",
        "Option4": "Joan Roca",
        "Answer": "Ferran Adrià"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 93,
        "Question": "The chef who is known for his use of technology in cooking and for his restaurant 'El Celler de Can Roca' is whom?",
        "Option1": "Ferran Adrià",
        "Option2": "Joan Roca",
        "Option3": "Andoni Luis Aduriz",
        "Option4": "Dabiz Muñoz",
        "Answer": "Joan Roca"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 94,
        "Question": "Who is the proprietor of 'The Fat Duck,' a three-Michelin-star restaurant in the UK?",
        "Option1": "Ferran Adrià",
        "Option2": "Heston Blumenthal",
        "Option3": "Massimo Bottura",
        "Option4": "Grant Achatz",
        "Answer": "Heston Blumenthal"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 95,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for his simple, rustic, and fresh approach to cooking, as seen on 'The Naked Chef'?",
        "Option1": "Gordon Ramsay",
        "Option2": "Jamie Oliver",
        "Option3": "Emeril Lagasse",
        "Option4": "Marco Pierre White",
        "Answer": "Jamie Oliver"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 96,
        "Question": "This chef is known for her television shows and cookbooks and is a major figure in the 'farm-to-table' movement.",
        "Option1": "Julia Child",
        "Option2": "Alice Waters",
        "Option3": "Ina Garten",
        "Option4": "Nancy Silverton",
        "Answer": "Alice Waters"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 97,
        "Question": "Which celebrity chef is famous for his signature catchphrase 'Bam!'?",
        "Option1": "Bobby Flay",
        "Option2": "Guy Fieri",
        "Option3": "Emeril Lagasse",
        "Option4": "Wolfgang Puck",
        "Answer": "Emeril Lagasse"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 98,
        "Question": "The chef and television personality who hosted 'No Reservations' and 'Parts Unknown' is who?",
        "Option1": "Anthony Bourdain",
        "Option2": "José Andrés",
        "Option3": "David Chang",
        "Option4": "Andrew Zimmern",
        "Answer": "Anthony Bourdain"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 99,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for popularizing 'California cuisine' and for his restaurant 'Spago'?",
        "Option1": "Wolfgang Puck",
        "Option2": "Thomas Keller",
        "Option3": "Alain Ducasse",
        "Option4": "Daniel Boulud",
        "Answer": "Wolfgang Puck"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 100,
        "Question": "Who is the author of 'Barefoot Contessa' cookbooks and the host of the television show of the same name?",
        "Option1": "Nigella Lawson",
        "Option2": "Ina Garten",
        "Option3": "Martha Stewart",
        "Option4": "Giada De Laurentiis",
        "Answer": "Ina Garten"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 101,
        "Question": "Which chef is a star of 'Beat Bobby Flay' and 'Iron Chef America,' and is known for his expertise in Southwestern and Tex-Mex cuisine?",
        "Option1": "Bobby Flay",
        "Option2": "Alton Brown",
        "Option3": "Michael Symon",
        "Option4": "Alex Guarnaschelli",
        "Answer": "Bobby Flay"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 102,
        "Question": "This chef is known for her '30 Minute Meals' television show and for her catchphrase 'EVOO'.",
        "Option1": "Ina Garten",
        "Option2": "Giada De Laurentiis",
        "Option3": "Rachael Ray",
        "Option4": "Paula Deen",
        "Answer": "Rachael Ray"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 103,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for his restaurant 'Daniel' and for being a master of contemporary French cuisine?",
        "Option1": "Jean-Georges Vongerichten",
        "Option2": "Alain Ducasse",
        "Option3": "Daniel Boulud",
        "Option4": "Joël Robuchon",
        "Answer": "Daniel Boulud"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 104,
        "Question": "Who is the youngest chef ever to be awarded three Michelin stars?",
        "Option1": "Jamie Oliver",
        "Option2": "Gordon Ramsay",
        "Option3": "Marco Pierre White",
        "Option4": "Heston Blumenthal",
        "Answer": "Marco Pierre White"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 105,
        "Question": "Known for his television show 'Bizarre Foods,' which chef travels the world to try unusual dishes?",
        "Option1": "Anthony Bourdain",
        "Option2": "Guy Fieri",
        "Option3": "Andrew Zimmern",
        "Option4": "Adam Richman",
        "Answer": "Andrew Zimmern"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 106,
        "Question": "Which American chef is known for her classic Italian dishes and her show 'Everyday Italian'?",
        "Option1": "Rachael Ray",
        "Option2": "Lidia Bastianich",
        "Option3": "Giada De Laurentiis",
        "Option4": "Ina Garten",
        "Answer": "Giada De Laurentiis"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 107,
        "Question": "Who is the proprietor of 'The French Laundry,' a renowned fine-dining establishment in California?",
        "Option1": "Daniel Humm",
        "Option2": "Thomas Keller",
        "Option3": "Eric Ripert",
        "Option4": "Grant Achatz",
        "Answer": "Thomas Keller"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 108,
        "Question": "This chef is known for his work with the 'Momofuku' restaurant group and for creating the television series 'Ugly Delicious'.",
        "Option1": "Grant Achatz",
        "Option2": "David Chang",
        "Option3": "Daniel Humm",
        "Option4": "José Andrés",
        "Answer": "David Chang"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 109,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for his humanitarian work and for founding the 'World Central Kitchen'?",
        "Option1": "José Andrés",
        "Option2": "Massimo Bottura",
        "Option3": "René Redzepi",
        "Option4": "Marcus Samuelsson",
        "Answer": "José Andrés"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 110,
        "Question": "The chef behind the 'farm-to-table' movement is who?",
        "Option1": "Julia Child",
        "Option2": "Alice Waters",
        "Option3": "Ina Garten",
        "Option4": "Nancy Silverton",
        "Answer": "Alice Waters"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 111,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for his television shows like 'Hell's Kitchen' and 'Kitchen Nightmares'?",
        "Option1": "Jamie Oliver",
        "Option2": "Gordon Ramsay",
        "Option3": "Heston Blumenthal",
        "Option4": "Tom Kerridge",
        "Answer": "Gordon Ramsay"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 112,
        "Question": "Who is the proprietor of the three-Michelin-star restaurant 'Osteria Francescana'?",
        "Option1": "Massimo Bottura",
        "Option2": "Carlo Cracco",
        "Option3": "Enrico Bartolini",
        "Option4": "Davide Oldani",
        "Answer": "Massimo Bottura"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 113,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for his avant-garde, 'molecular gastronomy' techniques, with a signature dish called 'Snail Porridge'?",
        "Option1": "Ferran Adrià",
        "Option2": "Heston Blumenthal",
        "Option3": "Massimo Bottura",
        "Option4": "Grant Achatz",
        "Answer": "Heston Blumenthal"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 114,
        "Question": "The chef and author who pioneered 'New American' cuisine, with his restaurant 'Spago', is whom?",
        "Option1": "Thomas Keller",
        "Option2": "Wolfgang Puck",
        "Option3": "Daniel Boulud",
        "Option4": "Bobby Flay",
        "Answer": "Wolfgang Puck"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 115,
        "Question": "Which chef is the proprietor of 'Alinea', a three-Michelin-star restaurant in Chicago known for its highly experimental cuisine?",
        "Option1": "Grant Achatz",
        "Option2": "Thomas Keller",
        "Option3": "José Andrés",
        "Option4": "Daniel Humm",
        "Answer": "Grant Achatz"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 116,
        "Question": "This chef is the owner of multiple restaurants and is known for his simple, rustic, and fresh approach to cooking.",
        "Option1": "Gordon Ramsay",
        "Option2": "Jamie Oliver",
        "Option3": "Emeril Lagasse",
        "Option4": "Marco Pierre White",
        "Answer": "Jamie Oliver"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 117,
        "Question": "Who is the proprietor of 'The Fat Duck,' a restaurant known for its multi-sensory and 'molecular gastronomy' approach?",
        "Option1": "Ferran Adrià",
        "Option2": "Massimo Bottura",
        "Option3": "Heston Blumenthal",
        "Option4": "Grant Achatz",
        "Answer": "Heston Blumenthal"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 118,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for his three-Michelin-star restaurant 'Le Bernardin' in New York City?",
        "Option1": "Thomas Keller",
        "Option2": "Eric Ripert",
        "Option3": "Daniel Boulud",
        "Option4": "Alain Ducasse",
        "Answer": "Eric Ripert"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 119,
        "Question": "This chef is the owner of 'L'Auberge du Pont de Collonges,' which held three Michelin stars for over 50 years.",
        "Option1": "Joël Robuchon",
        "Option2": "Paul Bocuse",
        "Option3": "Alain Ducasse",
        "Option4": "Auguste Escoffier",
        "Answer": "Paul Bocuse"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 120,
        "Question": "The chef behind the 'Momofuku' restaurant group is who?",
        "Option1": "David Chang",
        "Option2": "Danny Meyer",
        "Option3": "Thomas Keller",
        "Option4": "Mario Batali",
        "Answer": "David Chang"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 121,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for her show 'Barefoot Contessa' and for her approachable recipes?",
        "Option1": "Nigella Lawson",
        "Option2": "Ina Garten",
        "Option3": "Martha Stewart",
        "Option4": "Giada De Laurentiis",
        "Answer": "Ina Garten"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 122,
        "Question": "The chef behind the restaurant 'Noma,' which focuses on foraging and seasonal ingredients, is whom?",
        "Option1": "Claus Meyer",
        "Option2": "René Redzepi",
        "Option3": "Rasmus Kofoed",
        "Option4": "Magnus Nilsson",
        "Answer": "René Redzepi"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 123,
        "Question": "This chef is known for her '30 Minute Meals' television show and for her catchphrase 'EVOO'.",
        "Option1": "Ina Garten",
        "Option2": "Giada De Laurentiis",
        "Option3": "Rachael Ray",
        "Option4": "Paula Deen",
        "Answer": "Rachael Ray"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 124,
        "Question": "Who is the proprietor of the three-Michelin-star restaurant 'Osteria Francescana'?",
        "Option1": "Massimo Bottura",
        "Option2": "Carlo Cracco",
        "Option3": "Enrico Bartolini",
        "Option4": "Davide Oldani",
        "Answer": "Massimo Bottura"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 125,
        "Question": "Which chef is a star of 'Beat Bobby Flay' and 'Iron Chef America,' and is known for his expertise in Southwestern and Tex-Mex cuisine?",
        "Option1": "Bobby Flay",
        "Option2": "Alton Brown",
        "Option3": "Michael Symon",
        "Option4": "Alex Guarnaschelli",
        "Answer": "Bobby Flay"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 126,
        "Question": "This chef is known for his television show 'Good Eats' and for his scientific approach to cooking.",
        "Option1": "Michael Symon",
        "Option2": "Alton Brown",
        "Option3": "Tyler Florence",
        "Option4": "Alex Guarnaschelli",
        "Answer": "Alton Brown"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 127,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for his television show 'Bizarre Foods' and for trying unusual dishes?",
        "Option1": "Anthony Bourdain",
        "Option2": "Guy Fieri",
        "Option3": "Andrew Zimmern",
        "Option4": "Adam Richman",
        "Answer": "Andrew Zimmern"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 128,
        "Question": "The chef who is credited with inventing the sous-vide cooking method, and is the founder of 'El Celler de Can Roca' is whom?",
        "Option1": "Joan Roca",
        "Option2": "Ferran Adrià",
        "Option3": "José Andrés",
        "Option4": "Carme Ruscalleda",
        "Answer": "Joan Roca"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 129,
        "Question": "Which chef is the proprietor of the three-Michelin-star restaurant 'Le Bernardin'?",
        "Option1": "Thomas Keller",
        "Option2": "Eric Ripert",
        "Option3": "Daniel Boulud",
        "Option4": "Alain Ducasse",
        "Answer": "Eric Ripert"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 130,
        "Question": "This chef is known for her classic Italian dishes and her show 'Everyday Italian'.",
        "Option1": "Rachael Ray",
        "Option2": "Lidia Bastianich",
        "Option3": "Giada De Laurentiis",
        "Option4": "Ina Garten",
        "Answer": "Giada De Laurentiis"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 131,
        "Question": "Who is the proprietor of 'The French Laundry,' a renowned fine-dining establishment in California's Napa Valley?",
        "Option1": "Daniel Humm",
        "Option2": "Thomas Keller",
        "Option3": "Eric Ripert",
        "Option4": "Grant Achatz",
        "Answer": "Thomas Keller"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 132,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for his television shows like 'Hell's Kitchen' and 'MasterChef'?",
        "Option1": "Jamie Oliver",
        "Option2": "Gordon Ramsay",
        "Option3": "Heston Blumenthal",
        "Option4": "Tom Kerridge",
        "Answer": "Gordon Ramsay"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 133,
        "Question": "Who is the host of 'The F Word' and 'MasterChef,' and is known for his high standards and fiery temper?",
        "Option1": "Jamie Oliver",
        "Option2": "Gordon Ramsay",
        "Option3": "Heston Blumenthal",
        "Option4": "Marco Pierre White",
        "Answer": "Gordon Ramsay"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 134,
        "Question": "This chef is the owner of multiple restaurants, including 'Maze' and 'Petrus', and is a well-known television personality.",
        "Option1": "Jamie Oliver",
        "Option2": "Heston Blumenthal",
        "Option3": "Gordon Ramsay",
        "Option4": "Marco Pierre White",
        "Answer": "Gordon Ramsay"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 135,
        "Question": "Who is the proprietor of 'Nobu,' a chain of high-end Japanese restaurants known for their unique fusion cuisine?",
        "Option1": "Masaharu Morimoto",
        "Option2": "Nobu Matsuhisa",
        "Option3": "Tetsuya Wakuda",
        "Option4": "Jiro Ono",
        "Answer": "Nobu Matsuhisa"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 136,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for his simple, rustic, and fresh approach to cooking, as seen on 'The Naked Chef'?",
        "Option1": "Gordon Ramsay",
        "Option2": "Jamie Oliver",
        "Option3": "Emeril Lagasse",
        "Option4": "Marco Pierre White",
        "Answer": "Jamie Oliver"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 137,
        "Question": "This chef is the author of 'Barefoot Contessa' cookbooks and the host of the television show of the same name.",
        "Option1": "Nigella Lawson",
        "Option2": "Ina Garten",
        "Option3": "Martha Stewart",
        "Option4": "Giada De Laurentiis",
        "Answer": "Ina Garten"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 138,
        "Question": "The chef behind the 'Momofuku' restaurant group is who?",
        "Option1": "David Chang",
        "Option2": "Danny Meyer",
        "Option3": "Thomas Keller",
        "Option4": "Mario Batali",
        "Answer": "David Chang"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 139,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for his humanitarian work and for founding the 'World Central Kitchen'?",
        "Option1": "José Andrés",
        "Option2": "Massimo Bottura",
        "Option3": "René Redzepi",
        "Option4": "Marcus Samuelsson",
        "Answer": "José Andrés"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 140,
        "Question": "This chef is known for his television shows like 'Diners, Drive-Ins and Dives' and for his spiky hair.",
        "Option1": "Bobby Flay",
        "Option2": "Alton Brown",
        "Option3": "Michael Symon",
        "Option4": "Guy Fieri",
        "Answer": "Guy Fieri"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 141,
        "Question": "Which chef is the proprietor of 'The French Laundry,' a three-Michelin-star restaurant in Yountville, California?",
        "Option1": "Daniel Humm",
        "Option2": "Thomas Keller",
        "Option3": "Eric Ripert",
        "Option4": "Grant Achatz",
        "Answer": "Thomas Keller"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 142,
        "Question": "Who is the proprietor of the three-Michelin-star restaurant 'Osteria Francescana'?",
        "Option1": "Massimo Bottura",
        "Option2": "Carlo Cracco",
        "Option3": "Enrico Bartolini",
        "Option4": "Davide Oldani",
        "Answer": "Massimo Bottura"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 143,
        "Question": "The chef behind the restaurant 'Noma,' which focuses on foraging and seasonal ingredients, is whom?",
        "Option1": "Claus Meyer",
        "Option2": "René Redzepi",
        "Option3": "Rasmus Kofoed",
        "Option4": "Magnus Nilsson",
        "Answer": "René Redzepi"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 144,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for his television show 'Bizarre Foods' and for trying unusual dishes?",
        "Option1": "Anthony Bourdain",
        "Option2": "Guy Fieri",
        "Option3": "Andrew Zimmern",
        "Option4": "Adam Richman",
        "Answer": "Andrew Zimmern"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 145,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for her '30 Minute Meals' television show and for her catchphrase 'EVOO'?",
        "Option1": "Ina Garten",
        "Option2": "Giada De Laurentiis",
        "Option3": "Rachael Ray",
        "Option4": "Paula Deen",
        "Answer": "Rachael Ray"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 146,
        "Question": "This chef is known for her classic Italian dishes and her show 'Everyday Italian'.",
        "Option1": "Rachael Ray",
        "Option2": "Lidia Bastianich",
        "Option3": "Giada De Laurentiis",
        "Option4": "Ina Garten",
        "Answer": "Giada De Laurentiis"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 147,
        "Question": "Which chef is the proprietor of 'Alinea', a three-Michelin-star restaurant in Chicago?",
        "Option1": "Grant Achatz",
        "Option2": "Thomas Keller",
        "Option3": "José Andrés",
        "Option4": "Daniel Humm",
        "Answer": "Grant Achatz"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 148,
        "Question": "Who is the youngest chef ever to be awarded three Michelin stars?",
        "Option1": "Jamie Oliver",
        "Option2": "Gordon Ramsay",
        "Option3": "Marco Pierre White",
        "Option4": "Heston Blumenthal",
        "Answer": "Marco Pierre White"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 149,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for his television show 'Good Eats' and for his scientific approach to cooking?",
        "Option1": "Michael Symon",
        "Option2": "Alton Brown",
        "Option3": "Tyler Florence",
        "Option4": "Alex Guarnaschelli",
        "Answer": "Alton Brown"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 150,
        "Question": "This chef is a star of 'Beat Bobby Flay' and 'Iron Chef America,' and is known for his expertise in Southwestern and Tex-Mex cuisine.",
        "Option1": "Bobby Flay",
        "Option2": "Alton Brown",
        "Option3": "Michael Symon",
        "Option4": "Alex Guarnaschelli",
        "Answer": "Bobby Flay"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 151,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for his restaurant 'Daniel' and for being a master of contemporary French cuisine?",
        "Option1": "Jean-Georges Vongerichten",
        "Option2": "Alain Ducasse",
        "Option3": "Daniel Boulud",
        "Option4": "Joël Robuchon",
        "Answer": "Daniel Boulud"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 152,
        "Question": "The chef and proprietor of 'Osteria Francescana' is who?",
        "Option1": "Carlo Cracco",
        "Option2": "Massimo Bottura",
        "Option3": "Enrico Bartolini",
        "Option4": "Davide Oldani",
        "Answer": "Massimo Bottura"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 153,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for popularizing 'California cuisine' and for his restaurant 'Spago'?",
        "Option1": "Wolfgang Puck",
        "Option2": "Thomas Keller",
        "Option3": "Alain Ducasse",
        "Option4": "Daniel Boulud",
        "Answer": "Wolfgang Puck"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 154,
        "Question": "Who is the proprietor of 'The French Laundry,' a three-Michelin-star restaurant in Yountville, California?",
        "Option1": "Daniel Humm",
        "Option2": "Thomas Keller",
        "Option3": "Eric Ripert",
        "Option4": "Grant Achatz",
        "Answer": "Thomas Keller"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 155,
        "Question": "This chef is known for his humanitarian work and for founding the 'World Central Kitchen'.",
        "Option1": "José Andrés",
        "Option2": "Massimo Bottura",
        "Option3": "René Redzepi",
        "Option4": "Marcus Samuelsson",
        "Answer": "José Andrés"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 156,
        "Question": "The chef behind the 'Momofuku' restaurant group is who?",
        "Option1": "David Chang",
        "Option2": "Danny Meyer",
        "Option3": "Thomas Keller",
        "Option4": "Mario Batali",
        "Answer": "David Chang"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 157,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for his restaurant 'El Bulli' and for pioneering 'molecular gastronomy'?",
        "Option1": "Ferran Adrià",
        "Option2": "José Andrés",
        "Option3": "Massimo Bottura",
        "Option4": "Joan Roca",
        "Answer": "Ferran Adrià"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 158,
        "Question": "This chef is the owner of 'L'Auberge du Pont de Collonges,' a restaurant that held three Michelin stars for over 50 years.",
        "Option1": "Joël Robuchon",
        "Option2": "Paul Bocuse",
        "Option3": "Alain Ducasse",
        "Option4": "Auguste Escoffier",
        "Answer": "Paul Bocuse"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 159,
        "Question": "Who is the proprietor of 'The Fat Duck,' a restaurant known for its multi-sensory and 'molecular gastronomy' approach?",
        "Option1": "Ferran Adrià",
        "Option2": "Heston Blumenthal",
        "Option3": "Massimo Bottura",
        "Option4": "Grant Achatz",
        "Answer": "Heston Blumenthal"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 160,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for his humanitarian work with 'World Central Kitchen'?",
        "Option1": "José Andrés",
        "Option2": "Massimo Bottura",
        "Option3": "René Redzepi",
        "Option4": "Marcus Samuelsson",
        "Answer": "José Andrés"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 161,
        "Question": "The chef behind the 'Momofuku' restaurant group is who?",
        "Option1": "David Chang",
        "Option2": "Danny Meyer",
        "Option3": "Thomas Keller",
        "Option4": "Mario Batali",
        "Answer": "David Chang"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 162,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for her show 'Barefoot Contessa' and for her approachable recipes?",
        "Option1": "Nigella Lawson",
        "Option2": "Ina Garten",
        "Option3": "Martha Stewart",
        "Option4": "Giada De Laurentiis",
        "Answer": "Ina Garten"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 163,
        "Question": "The chef behind the restaurant 'Noma,' which focuses on foraging and seasonal ingredients, is whom?",
        "Option1": "Claus Meyer",
        "Option2": "René Redzepi",
        "Option3": "Rasmus Kofoed",
        "Option4": "Magnus Nilsson",
        "Answer": "René Redzepi"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 164,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for his television shows like 'Diners, Drive-Ins and Dives' and for his spiky hair?",
        "Option1": "Bobby Flay",
        "Option2": "Alton Brown",
        "Option3": "Michael Symon",
        "Option4": "Guy Fieri",
        "Answer": "Guy Fieri"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 165,
        "Question": "Which chef is a star of 'Beat Bobby Flay' and 'Iron Chef America,' and is known for his expertise in Southwestern and Tex-Mex cuisine?",
        "Option1": "Bobby Flay",
        "Option2": "Alton Brown",
        "Option3": "Michael Symon",
        "Option4": "Alex Guarnaschelli",
        "Answer": "Bobby Flay"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 166,
        "Question": "This chef is known for her '30 Minute Meals' television show and for her catchphrase 'EVOO'.",
        "Option1": "Ina Garten",
        "Option2": "Giada De Laurentiis",
        "Option3": "Rachael Ray",
        "Option4": "Paula Deen",
        "Answer": "Rachael Ray"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 167,
        "Question": "Who is the proprietor of the three-Michelin-star restaurant 'Osteria Francescana'?",
        "Option1": "Massimo Bottura",
        "Option2": "Carlo Cracco",
        "Option3": "Enrico Bartolini",
        "Option4": "Davide Oldani",
        "Answer": "Massimo Bottura"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 168,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for his avant-garde, 'molecular gastronomy' techniques, with a signature dish called 'Snail Porridge'?",
        "Option1": "Ferran Adrià",
        "Option2": "Heston Blumenthal",
        "Option3": "Massimo Bottura",
        "Option4": "Grant Achatz",
        "Answer": "Heston Blumenthal"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 169,
        "Question": "The chef and proprietor of 'Osteria Francescana' is who?",
        "Option1": "Carlo Cracco",
        "Option2": "Massimo Bottura",
        "Option3": "Enrico Bartolini",
        "Option4": "Davide Oldani",
        "Answer": "Massimo Bottura"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 170,
        "Question": "This chef is the owner of 'L'Auberge du Pont de Collonges,' a restaurant that held three Michelin stars for over 50 years.",
        "Option1": "Joël Robuchon",
        "Option2": "Paul Bocuse",
        "Option3": "Alain Ducasse",
        "Option4": "Auguste Escoffier",
        "Answer": "Paul Bocuse"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 171,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for his restaurant 'El Bulli' and for pioneering 'molecular gastronomy'?",
        "Option1": "Ferran Adrià",
        "Option2": "José Andrés",
        "Option3": "Massimo Bottura",
        "Option4": "Joan Roca",
        "Answer": "Ferran Adrià"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 172,
        "Question": "The chef who is credited with inventing the sous-vide cooking method, and is the founder of 'El Celler de Can Roca' is whom?",
        "Option1": "Joan Roca",
        "Option2": "Ferran Adrià",
        "Option3": "José Andrés",
        "Option4": "Carme Ruscalleda",
        "Answer": "Joan Roca"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 173,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for his humanitarian work with 'World Central Kitchen'?",
        "Option1": "José Andrés",
        "Option2": "Massimo Bottura",
        "Option3": "René Redzepi",
        "Option4": "Marcus Samuelsson",
        "Answer": "José Andrés"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 174,
        "Question": "This chef is the proprietor of 'Alinea', a three-Michelin-star restaurant in Chicago.",
        "Option1": "Grant Achatz",
        "Option2": "Thomas Keller",
        "Option3": "José Andrés",
        "Option4": "Daniel Humm",
        "Answer": "Grant Achatz"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 175,
        "Question": "Who is the proprietor of 'The French Laundry,' a three-Michelin-star restaurant in Yountville, California?",
        "Option1": "Daniel Humm",
        "Option2": "Thomas Keller",
        "Option3": "Eric Ripert",
        "Option4": "Grant Achatz",
        "Answer": "Thomas Keller"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 176,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for his fiery temper and is a star of shows like 'Hell's Kitchen' and 'Kitchen Nightmares'?",
        "Option1": "Jamie Oliver",
        "Option2": "Gordon Ramsay",
        "Option3": "Heston Blumenthal",
        "Option4": "Tom Kerridge",
        "Answer": "Gordon Ramsay"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 177,
        "Question": "The classic cookbook 'Mastering the Art of French Cooking' was co-authored by which American chef who brought French cuisine to the masses?",
        "Option1": "Ina Garten",
        "Option2": "Rachael Ray",
        "Option3": "Julia Child",
        "Option4": "Giada De Laurentiis",
        "Answer": "Julia Child"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 178,
        "Question": "Who is the host of 'The Naked Chef' and is famous for his simple, rustic, and fresh approach to cooking?",
        "Option1": "Gordon Ramsay",
        "Option2": "Jamie Oliver",
        "Option3": "Emeril Lagasse",
        "Option4": "Marco Pierre White",
        "Answer": "Jamie Oliver"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 179,
        "Question": "Which celebrity chef is famous for his signature catchphrases like 'Bam!' and 'Kick it up a notch!'?",
        "Option1": "Bobby Flay",
        "Option2": "Guy Fieri",
        "Option3": "Emeril Lagasse",
        "Option4": "Wolfgang Puck",
        "Answer": "Emeril Lagasse"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 180,
        "Question": "Known for his food-travel shows like 'No Reservations' and 'Parts Unknown,' which chef and author tragically passed away in 2018?",
        "Option1": "Anthony Bourdain",
        "Option2": "José Andrés",
        "Option3": "David Chang",
        "Option4": "Andrew Zimmern",
        "Answer": "Anthony Bourdain"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 181,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for her classic Italian dishes and her show 'Everyday Italian'?",
        "Option1": "Rachael Ray",
        "Option2": "Lidia Bastianich",
        "Option3": "Giada De Laurentiis",
        "Option4": "Ina Garten",
        "Answer": "Giada De Laurentiis"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 182,
        "Question": "This chef is known for her '30 Minute Meals' television show and for her catchphrase 'EVOO'.",
        "Option1": "Ina Garten",
        "Option2": "Giada De Laurentiis",
        "Option3": "Rachael Ray",
        "Option4": "Paula Deen",
        "Answer": "Rachael Ray"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 183,
        "Question": "Who is the proprietor of 'The French Laundry,' a renowned fine-dining establishment in California?",
        "Option1": "Daniel Humm",
        "Option2": "Thomas Keller",
        "Option3": "Eric Ripert",
        "Option4": "Grant Achatz",
        "Answer": "Thomas Keller"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 184,
        "Question": "Which chef is the proprietor of the three-Michelin-star restaurant 'Le Bernardin'?",
        "Option1": "Thomas Keller",
        "Option2": "Eric Ripert",
        "Option3": "Daniel Boulud",
        "Option4": "Alain Ducasse",
        "Answer": "Eric Ripert"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 185,
        "Question": "The chef behind the 'Momofuku' restaurant group is who?",
        "Option1": "David Chang",
        "Option2": "Danny Meyer",
        "Option3": "Thomas Keller",
        "Option4": "Mario Batali",
        "Answer": "David Chang"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 186,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for her show 'Barefoot Contessa' and for her approachable recipes?",
        "Option1": "Nigella Lawson",
        "Option2": "Ina Garten",
        "Option3": "Martha Stewart",
        "Option4": "Giada De Laurentiis",
        "Answer": "Ina Garten"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 187,
        "Question": "Who is the proprietor of 'Nobu,' a chain of high-end Japanese restaurants known for their unique fusion cuisine?",
        "Option1": "Masaharu Morimoto",
        "Option2": "Nobu Matsuhisa",
        "Option3": "Tetsuya Wakuda",
        "Option4": "Jiro Ono",
        "Answer": "Nobu Matsuhisa"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 188,
        "Question": "The chef behind the restaurant 'Noma,' which focuses on foraging and seasonal ingredients, is whom?",
        "Option1": "Claus Meyer",
        "Option2": "René Redzepi",
        "Option3": "Rasmus Kofoed",
        "Option4": "Magnus Nilsson",
        "Answer": "René Redzepi"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 189,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for his television shows like 'Diners, Drive-Ins and Dives' and 'Guy's Grocery Games'?",
        "Option1": "Bobby Flay",
        "Option2": "Alton Brown",
        "Option3": "Michael Symon",
        "Option4": "Guy Fieri",
        "Answer": "Guy Fieri"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 190,
        "Question": "This chef is a star of 'Beat Bobby Flay' and 'Iron Chef America,' and is known for his expertise in Southwestern and Tex-Mex cuisine.",
        "Option1": "Bobby Flay",
        "Option2": "Alton Brown",
        "Option3": "Michael Symon",
        "Option4": "Alex Guarnaschelli",
        "Answer": "Bobby Flay"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 191,
        "Question": "Who is the proprietor of the three-Michelin-star restaurant 'Osteria Francescana'?",
        "Option1": "Massimo Bottura",
        "Option2": "Carlo Cracco",
        "Option3": "Enrico Bartolini",
        "Option4": "Davide Oldani",
        "Answer": "Massimo Bottura"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 192,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for his avant-garde, 'molecular gastronomy' techniques, with a signature dish called 'Snail Porridge'?",
        "Option1": "Ferran Adrià",
        "Option2": "Heston Blumenthal",
        "Option3": "Massimo Bottura",
        "Option4": "Grant Achatz",
        "Answer": "Heston Blumenthal"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 193,
        "Question": "The chef behind the 'Momofuku' restaurant group is who?",
        "Option1": "David Chang",
        "Option2": "Danny Meyer",
        "Option3": "Thomas Keller",
        "Option4": "Mario Batali",
        "Answer": "David Chang"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 194,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for his humanitarian work and for founding the 'World Central Kitchen'?",
        "Option1": "José Andrés",
        "Option2": "Massimo Bottura",
        "Option3": "René Redzepi",
        "Option4": "Marcus Samuelsson",
        "Answer": "José Andrés"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 195,
        "Question": "This chef is the proprietor of 'Alinea', a three-Michelin-star restaurant in Chicago.",
        "Option1": "Grant Achatz",
        "Option2": "Thomas Keller",
        "Option3": "José Andrés",
        "Option4": "Daniel Humm",
        "Answer": "Grant Achatz"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 196,
        "Question": "Who is the proprietor of 'The French Laundry,' a three-Michelin-star restaurant in Yountville, California?",
        "Option1": "Daniel Humm",
        "Option2": "Thomas Keller",
        "Option3": "Eric Ripert",
        "Option4": "Grant Achatz",
        "Answer": "Thomas Keller"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 197,
        "Question": "This chef is the owner of 'L'Auberge du Pont de Collonges,' a restaurant that held three Michelin stars for over 50 years.",
        "Option1": "Joël Robuchon",
        "Option2": "Paul Bocuse",
        "Option3": "Alain Ducasse",
        "Option4": "Auguste Escoffier",
        "Answer": "Paul Bocuse"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 198,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for his restaurant 'El Bulli' and for pioneering 'molecular gastronomy'?",
        "Option1": "Ferran Adrià",
        "Option2": "José Andrés",
        "Option3": "Massimo Bottura",
        "Option4": "Joan Roca",
        "Answer": "Ferran Adrià"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 199,
        "Question": "The chef and proprietor of 'Osteria Francescana' is who?",
        "Option1": "Carlo Cracco",
        "Option2": "Massimo Bottura",
        "Option3": "Enrico Bartolini",
        "Option4": "Davide Oldani",
        "Answer": "Massimo Bottura"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 200,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for his simple, rustic, and fresh approach to cooking, as seen on 'The Naked Chef'?",
        "Option1": "Gordon Ramsay",
        "Option2": "Jamie Oliver",
        "Option3": "Emeril Lagasse",
        "Option4": "Marco Pierre White",
        "Answer": "Jamie Oliver"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 201,
        "Question": "Who is the proprietor of 'The Fat Duck,' a restaurant known for its multi-sensory and 'molecular gastronomy' approach?",
        "Option1": "Ferran Adrià",
        "Option2": "Heston Blumenthal",
        "Option3": "Massimo Bottura",
        "Option4": "Grant Achatz",
        "Answer": "Heston Blumenthal"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 202,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for his humanitarian work and for founding the 'World Central Kitchen'?",
        "Option1": "José Andrés",
        "Option2": "Massimo Bottura",
        "Option3": "René Redzepi",
        "Option4": "Marcus Samuelsson",
        "Answer": "José Andrés"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 203,
        "Question": "This chef is the owner of 'L'Auberge du Pont de Collonges,' a restaurant that held three Michelin stars for over 50 years.",
        "Option1": "Joël Robuchon",
        "Option2": "Paul Bocuse",
        "Option3": "Alain Ducasse",
        "Option4": "Auguste Escoffier",
        "Answer": "Paul Bocuse"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 204,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for her classic Italian dishes and her show 'Everyday Italian'?",
        "Option1": "Rachael Ray",
        "Option2": "Lidia Bastianich",
        "Option3": "Giada De Laurentiis",
        "Option4": "Ina Garten",
        "Answer": "Giada De Laurentiis"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 205,
        "Question": "Who is the proprietor of 'Nobu,' a chain of high-end Japanese restaurants known for their unique fusion cuisine?",
        "Option1": "Masaharu Morimoto",
        "Option2": "Nobu Matsuhisa",
        "Option3": "Tetsuya Wakuda",
        "Option4": "Jiro Ono",
        "Answer": "Nobu Matsuhisa"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 206,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for his television shows like 'Diners, Drive-Ins and Dives' and 'Guy's Grocery Games'?",
        "Option1": "Bobby Flay",
        "Option2": "Alton Brown",
        "Option3": "Michael Symon",
        "Option4": "Guy Fieri",
        "Answer": "Guy Fieri"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 207,
        "Question": "This chef is a star of 'Beat Bobby Flay' and 'Iron Chef America,' and is known for his expertise in Southwestern and Tex-Mex cuisine.",
        "Option1": "Bobby Flay",
        "Option2": "Alton Brown",
        "Option3": "Michael Symon",
        "Option4": "Alex Guarnaschelli",
        "Answer": "Bobby Flay"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 208,
        "Question": "Who is the proprietor of 'The French Laundry,' a renowned fine-dining establishment in California?",
        "Option1": "Daniel Humm",
        "Option2": "Thomas Keller",
        "Option3": "Eric Ripert",
        "Option4": "Grant Achatz",
        "Answer": "Thomas Keller"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 209,
        "Question": "The chef behind the 'Momofuku' restaurant group is who?",
        "Option1": "David Chang",
        "Option2": "Danny Meyer",
        "Option3": "Thomas Keller",
        "Option4": "Mario Batali",
        "Answer": "David Chang"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 210,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for her show 'Barefoot Contessa' and for her approachable recipes?",
        "Option1": "Nigella Lawson",
        "Option2": "Ina Garten",
        "Option3": "Martha Stewart",
        "Option4": "Giada De Laurentiis",
        "Answer": "Ina Garten"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 211,
        "Question": "This chef is known for her '30 Minute Meals' television show and for her catchphrase 'EVOO'.",
        "Option1": "Ina Garten",
        "Option2": "Giada De Laurentiis",
        "Option3": "Rachael Ray",
        "Option4": "Paula Deen",
        "Answer": "Rachael Ray"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 212,
        "Question": "Who is the proprietor of the three-Michelin-star restaurant 'Osteria Francescana'?",
        "Option1": "Massimo Bottura",
        "Option2": "Carlo Cracco",
        "Option3": "Enrico Bartolini",
        "Option4": "Davide Oldani",
        "Answer": "Massimo Bottura"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 213,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for his avant-garde, 'molecular gastronomy' techniques, with a signature dish called 'Snail Porridge'?",
        "Option1": "Ferran Adrià",
        "Option2": "Heston Blumenthal",
        "Option3": "Massimo Bottura",
        "Option4": "Grant Achatz",
        "Answer": "Heston Blumenthal"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 214,
        "Question": "The chef behind the 'Momofuku' restaurant group is who?",
        "Option1": "David Chang",
        "Option2": "Danny Meyer",
        "Option3": "Thomas Keller",
        "Option4": "Mario Batali",
        "Answer": "David Chang"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 215,
        "Question": "Which chef is known for his humanitarian work and for founding the 'World Central Kitchen'?",
        "Option1": "José Andrés",
        "Option2": "Massimo Bottura",
        "Option3": "René Redzepi",
        "Option4": "Marcus Samuelsson",
        "Answer": "José Andrés"
    },
    {
        "question_no.": 216,
        "Question": "This chef is the proprietor of 'Alinea', a three-Michelin-star restaurant in Chicago.",
        "Option1": "Grant Achatz",
        "Option2": "Thomas Keller",
        "Option3": "José Andrés",
        "Option4": "Daniel Humm",
        "Answer": "Grant Achatz"
    }
]